Mingyue Guo

E-mail: mquo28@my.centennialcollege.ca

Summary

I came to Canada in April 2021. I am friendly, dedicated, and hard-working. I have worked in China for more than 6 years at a single company. I resigned from the job in February 2021, as I was immigrating to Canada. I am a good team player and I am very honest and friendly with co-workers and clients. I enjoy learning new things and challenging myself. I am highly skilled at working with computers and software. Thank you for this opportunity and for taking the time to review my application.

Experience

July 2014 - February 2021

Name of Company: Xtayang Mechanical & Electrical Installation CO,. LTD,

Address: Shenzhen City, Guangdong Province, China

Job title: Accountant

- Responsible for recording all monthly bank transactions and financial expenditures of various departments into the financial system.
- Responsible for making financial statements.
- Responsible for managing part of the company's administrative work.
- Responsible for part of the company's human resources, travelling to local universities to recruit students for positions at the company.

November 2021- May 2022

Name of Company: Tim Hortons

Address: Whitby ON Canada

Education

September 2010 - June 2014

Name of school: Jilin Jianzhu University

Address: Xincheng St, Nanguan District, Changchun

Degree: Bachelor's degree

Major: Electronic Information Engineering